cloud-hosting-company.info 2015-10-21

# Privacy Policy - Cloud Hosting Company

**Effective: December 15, 2011**

cloud-hosting-company.info is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Web site. You can access cloud-hosting-company.info and browse our site without disclosing any of your personal data. cloud-hosting-company.info does not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which cloud-hosting-company.info will use it.

**Disclosure of Information**  
cloud-hosting-company.info will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track userís movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

If you do not want to have your information used in this way, send an e-mail message containing your name and email address to matt@cloud-hosting-company.info. cloud-hosting-company.info may release account information when such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law; enforce the terms of any of our user agreements; or protect the rights, property, and safety of cloud-hosting-company.info, the users of its site, or others.

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our sites from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under 18.

**External Web Sites**  
Please note that cloud-hosting-company.info contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information.

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by cloud-hosting-company.info. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact: info@cloud-hosting-company.info

**Affiliate Disclaimer**  
Nomadic Matt has financial relationships with some of the cards mentioned in this website, and cloud-hosting-company.info may be compensated if consumers choose to apply for these links in our content and ultimately sign up for them.
